Michael Caiati

332 Sloan Ct, Matawan, NJ 07751

732-890-2208 www.linkedin.com/in/michael-caiati

SUMMARY

mcaiati3@gmail.com

Analytical Technical Support professional adept at quickly troubleshooting and resolving customer concerns, communicating complex issues while establishing outstanding client relationships. Experience within SaaS cloud environment, collaborating with development and engineering teams to resolve isolated and platform wide issues.

SKILLS

MS Word · Excel · PowerPoint · Outlook · Filezilla · Salesforce · Zendesk · Jira · Microsoft Teams · Slack · Zoom · Skype for Business · Ring Central

EXPERIENCE

Technical Support Engineer III/TSE Product Specialist

iCIMS, Holmdel, NJ (July 2021 - Present)

- Act as the subject matter expert for the TextRecruit support team
- Work closely with software engineers to research/resolve complex problems
- Serve as mentor and senior product resource for level one and two TSEs
- Provide initial platform and queue management training for new hires

Technical Support Engineer II/TSE Specialized Product Support

iCIMS, Holmdel, NJ (June 2019 - Present)

- Provide technical/consultative support to customers regarding iCIMS platform and Text Engagement product, integration products and methodologies
- Work closely with customers to develop and provide customized solutions
- Troubleshoot programmable messaging issues and review error logs
- Distill complex resolution procedures into easily understood steps tailored for technical and non-technical customers
- Selected to participate in the Enterprise Customer Pilot Program to increase customer satisfaction with targeted enterprise clients
- Create training materials/presentations for iCIMS Text Engagement product
- Document all events and interactions in Zendesk, Salesforce and JIRA

Technical Support Engineer I

iCIMS, Holmdel, NJ (February 2018 – June 2019)

- Interact with customers via phone and email to resolve concerns and issues
- Independently collect and track information with details of the problem
- Responsible for learning iCIMS' ATS platform and ancillary products quickly and providing accurate information about them to customers

Policy Services Specialist

USI Affinity, Matawan, NJ (January 2015 – January 2018)

- Process, assemble and activate new and renewal insurance policies
- Modify, update and process existing policies to reflect any changes

EDUCATION

Pace University (New York, NY, August 2014)

• B.A., Communication Studies, magna cum laude